A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection, 1967-1993
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Thomas 5th Lord Fairfax, 1983 January; People-B43
- Thomas 6th Lord Fairfax, Undated; People-B44
- George and Anne Eilbeck Mason, Undated; People-B46
- Lawrence Washington, Undated; People-B47
- James Lee, Undated; People-B53
- James Lee, Undated; People-B54
- Sarah Tray, 1980 August; People-B55
- Nellie Custis, Undated; People-B57
- George and Anne Eilbeck Mason, Undated; People-B58
- George and Anne Eilbeck Mason, Undated; People-B59
- John Mosby, Undated; People-B60
- Sarah Tracy, Undated; People-B61
- Larry Moore, Staff Article, Undated; People-B62
- Pimmit Hills Development, Falls Church, VA, 1979 November; Pimmit-B1
- Pimmit Hills Development, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Pimmit-B2
- Asters beside the road, wild flowers near Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1972; Plan-Aste-1
- Wild Asters at Sully Historic District - back road, Chantilly, VA, 1972; Plan-Aste-2
- Pohick Bay Regional Park - Fern, 1973 August; Plan-Fern-1
- Pohick Bay Regional Park - Laurel Nurpa, c. 1975; Plan-Moun-1
- Pohick Bay Regional Park - Tree Fungus, 1973 August; Plan-Tree-F-1
- Pohick Church Front Elevation, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B1
- Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B4
- Pohick Church Administration Building, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B6
- Pohick Church Door, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B7
- Pohick Church Door, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B8
- Pohick Church Door, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B9
- Pohick Church Door, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B10
- Pohick Church Cemetery, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B12
- Pohick Church Cemetery, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B13
- Pohick Church Cemetery, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B14
- Pohick Church Cemetery, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B15
- Pohick Church District Fairfax County, Lorton, VA, 1990 November; Pohick-Church-B16
- Pohick Church Cemetery, Lorton, VA, 1969 September; Pohick-Church-B17
- Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1969 September; Pohick-Church-B18
- Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B19
- Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B20
- Pohick Church Cemetery - "For The Unknown Dead"- 1925, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B21
- Detail of Door Jamb, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B22
- Door Detail, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B23
- Old Tomb Stones at Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B24
- Old Tomb Stones at Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B25
- Drawing of Aerial View of Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, Undated; Pohick-Church-B26
- Aerial View of Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B27
- Aerial View of Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1981 November; Pohick-Church-B28
- Civil War Graffiti Written on Church Wall, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B29
- Civil War Graffiti Written on Church Wall, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B30
- Civil War Graffiti Written on Church Wall, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B31
- Civil War Graffiti Written on Church Wall, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B32
- Civil War Graffiti Written on Church Wall, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B33
- Graffiti On Wall at Pohick Church (Civil War), Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B34
- Graffiti On Wall at Pohick Church, Lorton, VA, 1990 March; Pohick-Church-B35
- Pope Leighey Interior, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Pope-Leighey-B1
- Pope Leighey Interior, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Pope-Leighey-B2
- Pope Leighy House, Alexandria, VA, 1984 September; Pope-Leighey-B3
- Pope Leighy House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Pope-Leighey-B4
- Pope Leighey House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Pope-Leighey-B5
- Popkins Farm House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Popkins-Farm-B1
- Popkins Farm House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Popkins-Farm-B2
- Barn at Popkins Farm, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Popkins-Farm-B3
- Barn at Popkins Farm, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Popkins-Farm-B4
- Population Chart 1790- 1975 (Fairfax), Undated; Population-B3
- Population Chart Fairfax County 1976; 1790- 1975, Undated; Population-B4
- Battle of Chantilly, September 1862, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Reed-B1
- Centreville - Looking over fortifications, June 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B2
- Centreville - Looking at fortifications, June 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B3
- Centreville - Sentry, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B4
- Centreville - Sentry, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B5
- Centreville - Army wagons, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B6
- Centreville - Army wagons, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B7
- Centreville - Marching, June 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B8
- Centreville - Marching, June 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B9
- Centreville - In tents, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B10
- Centreville, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B11
- Centreville, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B12
- Centreville, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B13
- Centreville, Va, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B14
- Centreville, Va, May 1863, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B15
- Centreville - Contraband slaves fleeing behing lines, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B16
- Centreville - Contraband slaves fleeing behing lines, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B17
- Centreville - Contraband slaves fleeing behing lines, Centreville, VA, Undated; Reed-B18
- Falls Church, 1862-1863, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Reed-B19
- Falls Church, 1862-1863, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Reed-B20
- Falls Church - Arillery sentry, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Reed-B21
- Falls Church - Arillery sentry, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Reed-B22
- Fort Ramsey - Two Calvarymen, January 1, 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B23
- Fort Ramsey - Calvarymen, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B24
- Fort Ramsey - Calvary on Hill, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B25
- Fort Ramsey - Calvary on Hill, March 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B26
- Fort Ramsey - Soldiers returned from furlough, April 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B27
- Fort Ramsey - Soldiers back from furlough, April 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B28
- Fort Ramsey - Carrying wood in snow, 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B29
- Fort Ramsey - Gambling, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B30
- Fort Ramsey - Carrying wood in snow, 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B31
- Fort Ramsey - Carrying wood in snow, 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B32
- Fort Ramsey - Digging rocks, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B33
- Fort Ramsey - Digging rocks, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B34
- Fort Ramsey - Artists equipment, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B35
- Fort Ramsey - Artists equipment, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B36
- Fort Ramsey - Roll call in rain, March 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B37
- Fort Ramsey - Roll call in rain, March 1864, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B38
- Fort Ramsey - Tent on Upton's Hill, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B39
- Fort Ramsey - Tent on Upton's Hill, November 23, 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B40
- Fort Ramsey - Entrance to Fort Ramsey, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B41
- Fort Ramsey - Entrance to Fort Ramsey, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B42
- Fort Ramsey - Man and horse, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B43
- Fort Ramsey - Man and horse, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B44
- Fort Ramsey - Quiet time in a soldiers life, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B45
- Fort Ramsey - Quiet time in a soldiers life, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B46
- Fort Ramsey - Campfire, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B47
- Fort Ramsey - Campfire, November 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B48
- Fort Ramsey - Soldiers folding blanket, March 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B49
- Fort Ramsey - Soldiers folding blanket, March 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B50
- Fort Ramsey - Soldier at door, April 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B51
- Fort Ramsey - Soldier in doorway, April 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B52
- Fort Ramsey - My tent, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B53
- Fort Ramsey - My tent, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B54
- Fort Ramsey - In tent, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B55
- Fort Ramsey - In tent, January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B56
- Fort Ramsey - Upton Hill, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B57
- Fort Ramsey - Upton Hill, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B58
- Fort Ramsey - Christmas dinner, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B59
- Fort Ramsey - Christmas dinner, December 1862, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B60
- Fort Ramsey - 6:30 a.m., January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B61
- Fort Ramsey - 6:30 a.m., January 1863, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Reed-B62
- Sunset Hills Gazebo, Reston, VA, 1972; Reston-B1
- Sunset Hills Gazebo, Reston, VA, 1972; Reston-B2
- Sunset Hills Distillery/Warehouse, Reston, VA, 1972; Reston-B6
- Terraset School, Reston, VA, Undated; Reston-B8
- Brown's Chapel, Reston, VA, Undated; Reston-B9
- Reston Walkway- Bridge, Reston, VA, Undated; Reston-B10
- Robey House Near Fairfax, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Robey-House-B1
- Robey House Near Fairfax, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Robey-House-B2
- Robinson House Near Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1977; Robinson-House-B2
- Robinson House Near Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1977; Robinson-House-B3
- Route 7 Widened Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Roads-B1
- Route 7 - c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B2
- Route 7 - c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B3
- Route 7 - c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B4
- Route 7 - c. 1920-1930, 1982 January; Roads-B5
- Jefferson Village Apartments Route 50, 1950, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Roads-B8
- Jefferson Village Apartments Route 50, 1950, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Roads-B10
- Jefferson Village Apartments Route 50, 1950, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Roads-B11
- Route 7 Bridge c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B12
- Route 7 Bridge, Undated; Roads-B13
- Route 7 Bridge, Undated; Roads-B14
- Old Dominion Drive, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Roads-B15
- Bellview Road, Great Falls, VA, 1989 March; Roads-B16
- Georgetown Pike, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Roads-B17
- Old Dominion Drive, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Roads-B18
- Middle Turnpike Road, Undated; Roads-B19
- Route 7 Bridge c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B20
- Route 7 - c. 1920-1930, Undated; Roads-B21
- Route 7 Widened Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Roads-B22
- Seven Corners, Seven Corners, VA, Undated; Roads-B23
- Paving Shirley Highway 1948, Undated; Roads-B25
- Stuck in Bad Road- Fairfax, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Roads-B26
- St. Mary's Church, Fairfax Station, VA, 1972 August; St-Mary-Church-B4
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B6
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B7
- Church from Fairfax Station Road, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 November; St-Mary-Church-B8
- Church from Fairfax Station Road.- 1st view from Route 123 Intersection, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 November; St-Mary-Church-B9
- St. Mary's Rectory - Fairfax Station, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B10
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B11
- Old Post Office - Fairfax Station, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B12
- Fairfax Station- Redone, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B13
- Fairfax Station- Redone, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B14
- Fairfax Station- Redone, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B15
- Fairfax Station- Redone, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 October; St-Mary-Church-B16
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B17
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B18
- St. Mary's Church, Fairfax Station, VA, 1972 August; St-Mary-Church-B20
- From Front Of Church View South to Shopping Center, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 November; St-Mary-Church-B21
- 1112 Fairfax Sta. Rd. 77-1-001-19 Rectory, Fairfax Station, VA, 1989 November; St-Mary-Church-B22
- St. Mary's Church District Fairfax County, Fairfax Station, VA, 1990 November; St-Mary-Church-B23
- Salona Village Shopping Center, McLean, VA, Undated; Salona-B5
- Salona Village Shopping Center, McLean, VA, Undated; Salona-B6
- Sully- Rear, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Sully-B1
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Sully-B2
- Sully - Rear, Chantilly, VA, 1971; Sully-B3
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B4
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1972; Sully-B6
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B7
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B8
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B9
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B10
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975; Sully-B11
- Sully - View From House, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Sully-B12
- Sully - Powerlines, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Sully-B13
- Sully Dairy, Chantilly, VA, 1980 January; Sully-B18
- School House- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1972; Sully-B19
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1975 August; Sully-B20
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1971 November; Sully-B14
- Sully, Chantilly, VA, 1971 November; Sully-B15
- 19th Century Cemetery Route 29 at Nutley St. Thompson Cemetery, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Thompson-Cemetery-B1
- Towlston Grange - Eibreitenbach, 1966, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Towlston-B1
- Towlston After Restoration, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Towlston-B2
- Tricketts-Colvin Run Rd. Front S.E. Side, Great Falls, VA, 1968; Tricketts-B1
- Tricketts-Colvin Run Rd. North Side, Great Falls, VA, 1968; Tricketts-B2
- Tricketts, Great Falls, VA, 1968; Tricketts-B3
- Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B1
- Vegetable Garden, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B2
- Animals in Medow at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B5
- Fence Building, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B6
- Pigsty - Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B7
- Split Rail Fence and Turkeys, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B8
- Split Rail Fence, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B9
- Orchard at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B10
- Turkeys - Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B11
- Tobacco Barn at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B12
- Tobacco Barn, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B13
- Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B15
- Razor Back Hog, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B16
- Razor Back Hog, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B17
- Razor Back Hog, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B18
- Razor Back Hog, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B19
- Razor Back Hog, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B20
- Razor Back Hog Shoat, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B21
- Razor Back Hogs, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B22
- Razor Back Hogs, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B23
- Razor Back Hog Shoat, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B24
- Tobacco Barn at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B25
- Fence Building at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B26
- Razor Back Hogs, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B27
- Tobacco Barn at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B28
- Cabin Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, 1979 October; Turkey-Run-FM-B29
- Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B30
- Cabin at Turkey Run Farm, McLean, VA, Undated; Turkey-Run-FM-B31
- Exterior View Of Turley Hall, Chantilly, VA, 1971 November; Turley-Hall-B1
- Turley Hall Exterior- In The Rain, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Turley-Hall-B2
- Turley Hall Exterior- In The Rain, Chantilly, VA, Undated; Turley-Hall-B3
- Turley Hall 34-2-001-10, Chantilly, VA, 1989 November; Turley-Hall-B4
- Bloomingdales-Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, Undated; Tysons-B4
- Bloomingdales-Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, Undated; Tysons-B5
- Bloomingdales-Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, Undated; Tysons-B6
- Tysons Area- Fire Department Photo, Tysons, VA, 1988; Tysons-B7
- Tysons Area- Fire Department Photo, Tysons, VA, 1988; Tysons-B8
- Tysons Area- Fire Department Photo, Tysons, VA, 1988; Tysons-B9
- Bloomingdales-Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, Undated; Tysons-B13
- Estate Colonial near Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, 1979; Tysons-B14
- Mount Vernon Influence Near Tysons Area, Tysons, VA, 1979; Tysons-B15
- Mount Vernon Influence Near Tysons Area, Tysons, VA, 1979; Tysons-B16
- Mount Vernon Influence Near Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, 1979; Tysons-B17
- Mount Vernon Influence Near Tysons Corner, Tysons, VA, 1979; Tysons-B18
- Tysons Corner Crossroads Market, 1963, Tysons, VA, Undated; Tysons-B19
- Windover Heights, Vienna, VA, 1989 October; Vienna-B2
- Black Church, First Baptist Church, Vienna, VA, Undated; Vienna-B4
- Louise Archer School, Vienna, VA, Undated; Vienna-B5
- Louise Archer School, Vienna, VA, Undated; Vienna-B6
- Nottoway Park? [possibly George Mason University Patriot Circle parking lot], Vienna, VA, Undated; Vienna-B7
- Wolftrap Farm Park, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B1
- Wolf Trap Park Performing Arts, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B2
- Wolftrap Farm Park For Performing Arts, Vienna, VA, 1979; Wolf-Trap-B3
- Wolf Trap Park for Performing Arts, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B4
- Filene Center Wolf Trap, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B5
- Filene Center Wolf Trap, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B6
- Filene Center Wolf Trap, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B7
- Wolf Trap Lawn Audience at Night, Vienna, VA, Undated; Wolf-Trap-B8
- Filene Stage - Wolf Trap, Vienna, VA, 1974 August; Wolf-Trap-B9
- Wolftrap Park Filene Center, Vienna, VA, 1979 November; Wolf-Trap-B10
- Woodaman Log Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1979 December; Woodaman-B2
- Woodaman Log Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1979 December; Woodaman-B3
- Woodaman Log Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1979 December; Woodaman-B4
- Woodaman Log Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1979 December; Woodaman-B5
- Woodaman Log Cabin, Fairfax, VA, 1979 December; Woodaman-B7
- Woodlawn on The Hill, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B2
- Woodlawn Pantation, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B11
- Woodlawn Friends Meeting House, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B12
- Custis Bedroom, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B13
- Custis Bedroom, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B14
- Dining Room at Woodlawn Plantation, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B15
- Playroom at Woodlawn Planation, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B16
- Sign: Woodlawn Meeting, Alexandria, VA, 1984 September; Woodlawn-B20
- Horse Shed: Quaker Meeting at Woodlawn, Alexandria, VA, 1984 September; Woodlawn-B22
- Woodlawn, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B23
- Woodlawn Custis Bedroom, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Woodlawn-B25
- West Elevation Grandview, Alexandria, VA, 1989 December; Woodlawn-B27
- Woodlawn District Fairfax County, Alexandria, VA, 1990 December; Woodlawn-B26
- Last Remaining Original Pew, Alexandria, VA, 1991 November; Woodlawn-Baptist-Church-B1
- Detail of the Ceiling, Alexandria, VA, 1991 November; Woodlawn-Baptist-Church-B2
- Original Ceiling Pulpit Area, Alexandria, VA, 1991 November; Woodlawn-Baptist-Church-B3